https://www.tronisoft.com/store/privacy-policy

Components
D-Type (D-SUB)
Privacy Policy
Tronisoft privacy policy shows how we use and protect any information that you give Tronisoft Limited when you use our website.Tronisoft is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and remains secure.If we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be confidentthat it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement and the law.Tronisoft Limited has the right to change this policy from time to time by updating this page.You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any of the changes.Cookie PolicyA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and thecookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you asan individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and rememberinginformation about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improveour website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data isremoved from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not.A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify yourbrowser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.Tronisoft Limited also use Session Cookies.Session Cookies are only stored temporarily in the browser's memory, and are destroyed when it is closed down,although they will survive navigating away from the website they came from.If you have to login to a website every time you open your browser and visit it - then it is using a session cookie to store your login credentials.Sites use session cookies and they can be deleted by clearing the cache and closing the website down.Tronisoft Collects the following information:contact information including email addressdemographic information such as postcode, preferences and interestsother information relevant to offersWhat we do with the information we gatherWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for thefollowing reasons:Internal record keeping & order processing.We may use the information to improve our products and services.We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information whichwe think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure,we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.Payments information are collected only from the payment processors site.  We do not store your card details online on our website.We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are requiredby law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information / items.You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small admin fee(currently £10) may be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held about you please write toTronisoft Limited, 12 Park Ln, Berkshire, Reading RG31 5AL.If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible,at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.TSPP - Effective Date 01/12/2018 - Rev 4
Tronisoft © 2020
Build v2.1
